Well, hello everyone and welcome to a
Englishspeaking video. I'm going to do
something a little bit different today.
I'm just going to have a straightup
conversation with you and I'm not going
to put any subtitles. You can simply
listen and in the comments you can share
what new vocabulary you heard, any new
sentences or phrase that you thought
were useful or some new things that
you'd like to learn or didn't
understand. Now, today I'm going to just
talk about some recent updates in my
life and uh I hope you enjoy it. So,
first of all, if you didn't know
already, I am a full-time content
creator. That means I make content on
all different social media platforms. I
have multiple accounts. My main one is
my English teaching account and my
second one is my more comedy
lifestyle vlogging account. So, I
started doing that one recently, my
second account. And I got to say it's
been really interesting.
I think that in life you have to
challenge yourself. You have to give
yourself like big goals. You need to mix
it up once in a while. I think that when
you're not being challenged every day,
when you're not learning something new,
you're not growing. And as you can see,
my my my main account, my English
accounts, they're quite popular. uh
million followers on each platform and
great engagement, great numbers. My
second account has been really
challenging. It's not getting exactly
the numbers I'd like to see. It doesn't
get that instant gratification of big
viral numbers, big viral hits, and it's
been very, what's the right word? It's
been very um
humbling.
So by humbling I mean that it's it's
been very
uh humbling to start from the beginning
again to feel that feeling of failure to
kind of feel like oh man like do I suck?
Do people not like me? Do do people not
care about what I'm saying or doing? But
I'm very grateful for the opportunity.
In a sense it is kind of lit a fire
under my my uh my my butt. Sorry, I
can't curse in these videos. And it's
really
encouraged me to kind of really work
harder than I have before. And also, I
feel that it's kind of challenged me to
be more disciplined, to really think
outside the box, to really up my game in
a lot of different ways.
So, I feel like overall this new
challenge is making me a better content
creator in in in all different aspects.
For example, script writing, editing,
um just just just everything because now
I'm trying new things and I'm looking at
things from different angles. I I'm
doing research and so yeah, that's been
an interesting uh challenge for me in my
recent life. Now, the funny observation
I've seen is that a lot of comedy
accounts, this is really funny. So, you
know, sometimes you'll watch like a a
really viral video, like a meme or
something like that, and then you'll you
you'll you'll see it and you say, "Wow,
that that that was really original."
Right? The thing is, when I started
doing research on like these funny viral
videos, I've noticed, wait a minute,
this person's doing that video as well.
that person's doing that video as well.
Seems like everybody's doing the same
video. And so it makes you wonder all
these comedy accounts,
are any of them really original or is it
more so like, okay, that person did it
better, that person did it better. In
fact, some videos I've read in the
comments, they say, "Oh, you were the
original, but this person did it better.
They at this person, this person won the
trend." So, it's funny. It it it makes
me think about, you know, originality,
you know, content creation ideas. For
me, I I'm I'm really proud of myself
because honestly,
I I can say to you, and I mean this, I'm
not trying to brag, for my English
teaching content, my my my second comedy
account,
I try my best to not copy anybody. In
fact, this is the reason why I don't
even watch social media. I I rarely do.
I don't scroll through videos because I
don't want to indirectly
copy someone, you know? I don't want to
be like, "Oh, that's a good idea. Maybe
I should copy it." Now, I'm not going to
pretend that I'm everything is original.
Right? Sometimes I do see something
that's really amazing, but I do try my
best to rewrite the script and kind of
make sure okay if if if the end result
is going to be this way, the way towards
there could be a little bit different.
Okay, so that kind of begs the question,
you know, that and if you're still here,
I appreciate it. It begs the question
for me a as a content creator. I'm
always curious about what do my viewers
want?
What do you like watching?
Could you let me know like my videos?
Why do you watch my videos? What's the
appeal? Why do you enjoy them? Why do
you binge watch them? Hopefully,
why do you like me? What is it about my
content that you like? You know, there
are so many other content creators. I
think if I were to put some words in
your mouth, I think one thing for me I
can confidently say is that I do feel
that I am quite original and I really
try to make my English lessons fun. You
know, I could be very serious like,
okay, today we're going to learn about
grammar. Today we're going to learn some
advanced vocabulary, this, this, this,
that, that. But I feel, at least for me,
that
learning is more interesting. It's
easier when it's fun.
You know, when you're having a good
time, things get easier. And so, this is
why I try to avoid being too serious in
my English lessons. This is why I really
try my best to make things fun and
interesting. And so that also includes
improving my acting skills, uh putting
more comedy in my skits, uh really
putting in that extra effort. So I would
love for you to give your feedback to me
as well. You know, like I told you
before, I'm trying new things. I am
trying to step out of my comfort zone.
I'm really trying my best to really grow
as a content creator. I think this year
especially,
I've made a lot of big leaps and bounds
in my career and I feel right now I'm in
a good spot. I feel right now the sky is
the limit. I I've been doing this for a
long time, you know, over 10 or 15
years, but it it really wasn't until a
few years ago that I started to see some
real success.
Thankfully, right now I'm in a good spot
where
the harder I work, I'm guaranteed a
result. The problem is as I'm getting
older, I'm not that old, but you know,
as I'm getting to middle age,
I'm finding I want to do more. I want to
do so much more, but at the end of the
day, I'm tired. I want to take a break.
I don't have that that urge like that
that fire that I did when I was in my
early 20s anymore.
So I don't know if this is being too
comfortable because I am successful or
is it just laziness? Is it just
procrastination?
Is it just I don't have that fire like I
used to. So again that's why I've been
trying to step out of my comfort zone.
Do new things. This is a new thing.
Talking to you like this, you know, in
public, doing this long form video is is
something new as well.
So, I guess that the the point of what
I'm trying to say is that I'm on a great
journey right now and I'm very happy to
have you here with me along for the
ride. And I do want to thank you all for
your support and I do want to thank you
all for really commenting, engaging my
content. You know, I get so many
comments. I wish I could respond to all
of you, but I can't. But I do want to
take the time to say in this video,
thank you so much for everything. And I
love you. I really do. Without your
support, I wouldn't be here right now
doing this and making a living out of
doing content. Okay. So, anyways, my
friends, that's the end of this video,
but I would like you in the comments,
what do you think about this type of
content?
Did you learn any new words or phrases?
What was useful for you? I would like
you to please tell me in the comments
and and also too if you understood
everything share your thoughts. How
could I do things better? You know, how
could I motivate myself more? How could
I improve? How could I stay more
disciplined? Share your thoughts with me
in the comments. And if this is your
first time here, thank you so much.
Don't forget to like, subscribe, and
follow. And I will see you next time.
Bye.